Guide to the Huffington and allied families' papers, 1650-1955 MS 883
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series V: Oversize
  - 1850 Census of Talbot County, Maryland, 1998 (Box 8, Item 11)
  - 1850 Census of Caroline County, Maryland, Undated (Box 8, Item 12)
  - 1870 Census of Baltimore City, Maryland, 1998 (Box 8, Item 13)
  - 1880 Census of Baltimore City, Maryland, 1998 (Box 8, Item 14)
  - 1880 Census of Wicomico County, Maryland, 1998 (Box 8, Item 15)
  - 1900 Census of Baltimore County, Maryland, Undated (Box 8, Item 16)
  - 1900 Census of Wicomico County, Maryland, 1998 (Box 8, Item 17)
  - 1900 Census of Baltimore City, Maryland, Undated (Box 8, Item 18)
  - 1900 Census of Washington, District of Columbia, Undated (Box 8, Item 19)
  - 1910-1920 Censuses of Easton, Talbot County, Maryland, 1998 (Box 8, Item 20)
  - 1800 Census of Somerset County, Maryland, 1998 (Box 9, Item 1)
  - 1810 Census of Sussex County, Delaware, 1998 (Box 9, Item 2)
  - Volunteers for War of 1812, Maryland and Delaware, 1998 (Box 9, Item 3)
  - 1820 Census of Little Creek, Sussex County, Delaware, Undated (Box 9, Item 4)
  - 1820 Census of Sussex County, Delaware, 1998 (Box 9, Item 5)
  - 1830 Census of Sussex County, Delaware, 1998 (Box 9, Item 6)
  - 1840 Census of Dagsborough One Hundred, Sussex County, Delaware, 1998 (Box 9, Item 7)
  - 1850 Census of New Castle County, Delaware, Undated (Box 9, Item 8)
  - 1850 Censuses of Queen Anne Creek County and Somerset County, Maryland, 1998 (Box 9, Item 9)
  - 1850 Slave Schedules for District Number One, Dorchester County, Maryland, 1998 (Box 9, Item 10)
  - 1850 Census of Eleventh Subdivision, Sussex County, Delaware, Undated (Box 9, Item 11)
  - 1850 Census of Wilmington, Delaware, Undated (Box 9, Item 12)
  - 1860-1870 Censuses of Smyrna, Kent County, Delaware, 1998 (Box 9, Item 13)
  - General Index to Pension Files, 1861-1934, 1998 (Box 9, Item 14)
  - 1870-1880 Censuses of Grenada, Mississippi, Undated (Box 9, Item 15)
  - 1870 Census of Wilmington, Delaware, Undated (Box 9, Item 16)
  - 1880 Census of Guelph Township, Sumner County, Kansas, 1998 (Box 9, Item 17)
  - 1900 Census of Indiana, 1998 (Box 9, Item 18)
  - 1900 Census of Kings County, New York, 1998 (Box 9, Item 19)
  - 1900 Census of Philadelphia County, Pennsylvania, 1998 (Box 9, Item 20)
  - 1920 Census of Grenada, Mississippi, Undated (Box 9, Item 21)
  - Will of Francis F. Brown, 1755, 1969 (Box 10, Item 1)
  - Mecklenburg County Deed Books, 1773-1801, 1963 (Box 10, Item 2)
  - Revolutionary War Register, 1968 (Box 10, Item 3)
  - Brunswick County Deed Book 15, 1790-1794, 1964 (Box 10, Item 4)
  - Will of Beverly Brown, 1791, 1964 (Box 10, Item 5)
  - Charlotte County, Virginia Tax Lists, 1797-1804, Undated (Box 10, Item 6)
  - Charlotte County, Virginia Taxables, 1798, Undated (Box 10, Item 7)
  - Charlotte County Deed Book 10, 1803-1806, 1963 (Box 10, Item 8)
  - Charlotte County, Virginia Tax List, 1805, Undated (Box 10, Item 9)
  - Charlotte County Deed Books, 1806-1823, 1963 (Box 10, Item 10)
  - 1830 Census of Franklin County, Missouri, Undated (Box 10, Item 11)
  - Will of James Brown, 1830, 1963 (Box 10, Item 12)
  - 1860 Census of South Ward, St. Louis City, Missouri, Undated (Box 10, Item 13)
  - Deed of Gift from George P. Dorriss and Sarah Henderson Dorriss, 1860, 1971 (Box 10, Item 14)
  - Sarah Henderson Dorriss Quit Claim, 1895, 1971 (Box 10, Item 15)
  - Marks of Hanover County, Virginia, Undated (Box 10, Item 16)
  - 1810 Census of Broadcreek, Somerset County, Maryland, 1998 (Box 11, Item 1)
  - 1820 Census of Somerset County, Maryland, 1998 (Box 11, Item 2)
  - 1820-1830 Censuses of Dorchester County, Maryland, 1998 (Box 11, Item 3)
  - 1850 Census of Lawrence County, Indiana, 1998 (Box 11, Item 4)
  - 1850 Census of Marion County, Indiana, 1998 (Box 11, Item 5)
  - 1850 Census of Trappe District, Somerset County, Maryland, 1998 (Box 11, Item 6)
  - 1850-1870 Censuses of York County, Virginia, 1998 (Box 11, Item 7)
  - 1860 Census of Clark County, Illinois, 1998 (Box 11, Item 8)
  - 1860-1870 Censuses of Buchanan County, Missouri, 1998 (Box 11, Item 9)
  - 1860 Census of Sussex County, New Jersey, 1998 (Box 11, Item 10)
  - 1870 Census of Lawrence County, Indiana, 1998 (Box 11, Item 11)
  - 1880 Census of Clark County, Illinois, 1998 (Box 11, Item 12)
  - 1900 Census of Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1998 (Box 11, Item 13)
  - 1900 Census of Crooked Creek Township, Jasper County, Illinois, 1998 (Box 11, Item 14)
  - 1900 Census of McLean County, Illinois, 1998 (Box 11, Item 15)
  - 1900 Census of Vermillion County, Illinois, 1998 (Box 11, Item 16)
  - 1900 Census of Delta County, Colorado, Undated (Box 11, Item 17)
  - 1910 Census of Warren County, Virginia, 1998 (Box 11, Item 18)
  - 1910-1920 Censuses of Denton County, Texas, 1998 (Box 11, Item 19)
  - 1920 Census of New York City, New York, 1998 (Box 11, Item 20)
  - Land Records of Worchester County, Maryland, 1778, 1994 (Box 12, Item 1)
  - Tax Lists of Accomack County, 1693-1695, Undated (Box 12, Item 2)
  - Dorchester County 1800 and 1810, 1998 (Box 12, Item 3)
  - 1830 Census of Simpson County, Kentucky, 1998 (Box 12, Item 4)
  - 1850 Slave Schedules for Dorchester County, Maryland, Undated (Box 12, Item 5)
  - 1850 Census of Baltimore City, Maryland, 1998 (Box 12, Item 6)
  - 1850-1860 Censuses of Marion County, Indiana, 1998 (Box 12, Item 7)
  - 1850-1860 Censuses of Sussex County, Laurel, Delaware, Undated (Box 12, Item 8)
  - 1860 Censuses of Virginia, Undated (Box 12, Item 9)
  - 1860 Census of Chester County, Pennsylvania, 1998 (Box 12, Item 10)
  - 1860 Census of Jefferson County, Kentucky, Undated (Box 12, Item 11)
  - 1870 Census of Sussex County, Laurel, Delaware, Undated (Box 12, Item 12)
  - 1880 Census of Cherokee County, Kansas, 1998 (Box 12, Item 13)
  - 1880 Census of Trappe District, Wicomico County, Maryland, 1998 (Box 12, Item 14)
  - 1900 Census of Marion County, Indiana, 1998 (Box 12, Item 15)
  - 1900 Census of Center Township, Marion County, Indiana, Undated (Box 12, Item 16)
  - 1900 Census of Philadelphia City, Pennsylvania, 1998 (Box 12, Item 17)
  - 1900-1910 Censuses of Seaford Town, Sussex County, Delaware, 1998 (Box 12, Item 18)
  - 1910 Census Index of Texas, 1998 (Box 12, Item 19)
  - 1920 Census of Saranac Lake, Franklin County, New York, 1998 (Box 12, Item 20)
  - Maryland Privateers, 1812, 1998 (Box 13, Item 1)
  - 1820 Census of Dorchester County, Maryland, 1998 (Box 13, Item 2)
  - 1820 Census of Delaware, 1998 (Box 13, Item 3)
  - 1830 Census of Sussex County, Undated (Box 13, Item 4)
  - 1840 Census of Broadcreek One Hundred, Sussex County, Delaware, Undated (Box 13, Item 5)
  - 1850 Censuses of Illinois, 1998 (Box 13, Item 6)
  - 1850 Census of New Jersey, 1998 (Box 13, Item 7)
  - 1850 Census of District One, Dorchester County, Maryland, 1998 (Box 13, Item 8)
  - 1850 Census of Fourth Ward, Baltimore City, Maryland, 1998 (Box 13, Item 9)
  - 1850 Census of Champaign County, Illinois, Undated (Box 13, Item 10)
  - 1860 Census of Little Creek, Sussex County, Delaware, Undated (Box 13, Item 11)
  - 1870 Census of Clark County, Illinois, Undated (Box 13, Item 12)
  - 1880 Census of Anderson Township, Clark County, Illinois, 1998 (Box 13, Item 13)
  - 1880 Census of Baltimore, Maryland, 1998 (Box 13, Item 14)
  - 1880 Census of Franklin Township, Marion County, Indiana, 1998 (Box 13, Item 15)
  - 1880 Census of Number Eight Neck District, Dorchester County, Maryland, 1998 (Box 13, Item 16)
  - 1900 Census of Lake County, Indiana, 1998 (Box 13, Item 17)
  - 1900-1910 Censuses of New Castle County, Delaware, Undated (Box 13, Item 18)
  - Fourteenth Census of the United States: 1920 Military and Naval Population Abroad, 1998 (Box 13, Item 19)
  - 1920 Census of York County, Virginia, Undated (Box 13, Item 20)
  - Henry W. Gough Oversized Photographs, 1900 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - John Edwin Gough and Celeste Brown Gough Oversized Photographs, 1910-1941 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Roy M. Huffington Oversized Photographs and Certificates, 1917-2000 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Roy Mackey Huffington Oversized Certificates, 1918 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - C. Phyllis Gough Huffington Oversized Photographs and Certificates, 1931-1945 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Marie Hook Brown Lyle Mounted Photograph, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Huffington Relatives Mounted Photographs, 1946 (Box 14, Folder 7)